I had taken installment plus agreement but the
reading is installed brother it is gold and cup some
on de queen
only card what is his financial number na kare
and from time mandir you get builder
number because it is going inside
guru bhai my name is Jagdish ok this
guy first went to my shop the day before yesterday he went to my
shop when he went to my house I was
not there I was not present then after
searching he came to my shop I don't know
who gave me my address so he came to this address ok no
problem it is his work he is following you let him
call I did
not say anything to him also then the day before yesterday I had
forgotten to make a video I all
three-four people came to my shop look the guy was
standing outside and three people are inside me one guy
started making a video I brother tell me
where did you come from you video he said we
withdraw ID card from such and such bank he does not have it
ok and phone letter has not been answered
ok so I asked him what happened if the
money is left then when are you paying the money I do not have it right now I do
not have it I will
pay the money when I have it then he said no no I
need the money tomorrow  I need money tomorrow, tomorrow is the matter, I do
n't have money, you can do whatever you want
brother,
but I will have money tomorrow, I do
n't have money even to eat, I
told him my decision like this, before that I had
also gone to his branch, I don't want these people, recovery
people come to do their hooliganism,
so Banda started making a video, so I
told him that brother I don't have money,
when I come in future I will give it to you, I will
settle it, for
how much will I settle it, then he has to say that
you give me ₹10000, so the total amount of money
received in the house is 130 thousand, then
give me 95, I will not settle it like this in the setter, I don't have
money, I do
n't have money to eat poison, when I have money
I will settle it for you tomorrow, then he has to
say that okay I will do it for 50%, I will
forget 50%, I do
n't have money to eat poison, I completely
agreed to him and said that I don't have money at all, I do
n't have money to eat poison, so he has to
say that when I have  When I come, I will give the
last 15% of my money up to this 20%, I will
not be able to do more than this, I do
not have the means, if you go you can do it legally, you can do
anything brother, then if it comes to hooliganism, then there was
a guy, he had gone out,
I made a video, okay, so I did
something to him, then what about me tomorrow,
okay, because of yesterday, while I was
attending his call, I have a video, everything happened
extra there, then you will say that
hooliganism had also come, okay, then I was
not able to make a video of it, okay, then
those people, then I was also taken out, then those
people had gone, okay, this is how
we talked, okay,
these people were not even talking about settlement, they say that
people are doing hooliganism, nothing else,
after that there is no system other than hooliganism,
okay,